

FAIZ SHARIFF

- +91 9620964210
- btm layout ,bangalore
- faizshariff540@gmail

About me

floor am a reliable, creative and hardworking professional, adept at working in teams and on my own initiative. I continually strive to stay ahead of the curve with the latest trends and frameworks while embracing the challenge of problem-solving additionally, I'm experienced in software development and design, and mainly focus on growing while helping others.

Experience



TECHKIT - Bangalore

Frontend Engineer: Jul 2022 - Nov 2022

At Techkit I had the opportunity to successfully utilize my skills to design & develop a top-tier online presence for the company with the help of nextjs, sanity and tailwind css ,therefore making it possible to attract a larger audience and new potential customers



Urban Gifts - Bangalore

Wordpress Developer: Jun 2021 - Nov 2021

I solved complex issues at Urban Gifts by creating an E-commerce site to help them reach their target audience and constantly updating and maintaining the site. this experience provided me with a wealth of knowledge that has enhanced my capabilities

Education



SSMRV

BCA - CS Jun 2021 - May 2024



VCPUC

PUC - PCMC 2019 - 2021

ST THOMAS

- 10TH - CBSE 2008 - 2018

Skills



NEXT.JS



REACT-NATIVE



TYPESCRIPT



REDUX



Tailwind css



WORDPRESS











